Preliminary Guide to the History Department records, 1905-2001 RG0073
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Edward Berkowitz papers, 1935-2001; RG0073 Series 7; 9 Linear Feet
  - Class material, 1946-2001; Series 6 Subseries 1; 6 Linear Feet
    - Liapis, Kathy, 2000; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2, Folder data_value_missing_ddde9b5db6ed9a29c3cea950b3d6adc1)
    - Lichtenstein Project, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3, Folder data_value_missing_9bc89a840f6ea95fc8eae5d57e0d948a)
    - MA in Public Policy, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4, Folder data_value_missing_f6a6b4ba323e6d6c18dc9311f9cbad31)
    - Marketing list, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5, Folder data_value_missing_c008e4aa105d8a6ab4a69edcd3c11167)
    - McQuaid, Kim, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6, Folder data_value_missing_b0210a361000f485ae3192ed454fdd0f)
    - Medical Follow-Up Agency, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 7, Folder data_value_missing_785cda729502e1d0bd7c91bf23d0c6ef)
    - Mental Retardation: A Case Study, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 8, Folder data_value_missing_e5f67c8c0f63f819a80a1fcd81307d1c)
    - Mental Retardation: Kennedy Library Conference, 1983-1984; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 9, Folder data_value_missing_414cef46e4a0741af985e768319ef971)
    - Mental Retardation Project, 1984; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 10, Folder data_value_missing_f38ff1e8964b214b3aae0c9cd633260b)
    - Millbank Memorial Fund, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 11, Folder data_value_missing_23a086f0f73ed2442180009e05d5ac2e)
    - The Miller Center, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 12, Folder data_value_missing_26d55b28abc05c010c7b8d406f1ccf9f)
    - Morian, Armen, 1999; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 13, Folder data_value_missing_570427e54d6421b0164e7357baaabab3)
    - Moynihan Report, 1965; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 14, Folder data_value_missing_6108aa37c83c946f3727c148cefc0a10)
    - Modern Europe Appointment, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Mt. Vernon Ladies Association, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Muffled Boom in the Labor Market, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - NASI Book of Readings, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - NASI January 11 Seminar, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - NASI - Disability Project, 1994-1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance History Project, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - NASI, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - New York Times, 1961; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Articles, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Nicholson, Ronald A. Medicare Proposal, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - NIMH Project: Cantelon, 1983-1984; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Oxford Companion, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Oxford University, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Papers on 1970s, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Patterson, Tom, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Personnel, 1982; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Pfeffer, Paula, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Playing Fair with the Past, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Pohlman, Ken: The Emergence of Modern Rehabilitation, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Praeger, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - President's Commission for a National Agenda for the 80s, 1980; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, 1963; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Professional Analysis/Articles, 1963; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Promoting Welfare of Americans in 80s, 1980; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Prudential, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Public Historian, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Public History Essays, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Public Policy Toward Disability, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Public Policy Grad Program Development, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Public Policy Toward Rehabilitation of the Occupationally Disabled, 1975-1979; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Publications, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Radosh, Ronald, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Raleigh Essay, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Raskin, Marcus, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Raynor, Greg, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - REIA, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Research in Social Science and Disability, 1998-2000; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Reviews in American History, 1983-1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ribicoff's Papers, 1961; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ribicoff's Papers, 1961; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sachem Publications, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Savage, Barbara, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Sealander, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Seelieb-Kaiser, Martin, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Society of Archivists, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Social Security, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Smolova, Tatiyana, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Social Security 50th Anniversary, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Social Security Reform, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Social Welfare Project, 1979; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Society of Actuaries, 1999; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Space, 2000; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - The State - 91, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Mary Suitzer: Entrepreneur Within the Welfare State, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Sullivan, Brian, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Supporting Disability, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Survey, 1991; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Sweden Conference, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Syllabi and student evaluations, 1986-1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Seminar: Teaching Survey Courses, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Thayer, Fred, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Unemployment, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - UNIM, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Unem, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - University History, 1994; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - University of Kansas Press, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Vanderbilt, 2000; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Wagley, Stephen, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Washington Post, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Reform, 1978-1980; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Welfare Reform, 1976-1980; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Welfare Reform, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - West, Jane, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Wilbur Cohen material and memorabilia, 1988; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Wilbur Mills, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Wheelchair Project, 1999; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Williamsburg, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Wilson Center Project, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Women's National Democratic Club, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Work History, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The World and I, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Wrinn, Stephen, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Papers and publications, 1935-2000; Series 7 Subseries 2; 2 Linear Feet
    Materials in this subseries relate to materials written and/or published by Edward Berkowitz. This includes book reviews and articles. The material dates from 1935-2000.
    - "An American Perspective on Disability Programs", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - America's Welfare State, 1991; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - America's Welfare State, 1992; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Bureaucrats as Social Engineers, 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - "Businessman and Bureaucrat", 1978-1983; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Coal-Mining in The Progressive Period, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Commentary on Deborah Street and Jill Quadagno: 'The State, the Elderly and the Intergenerational Contract: Toward a New Political Economy of Aging'", 1991; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Commissioning the Future", 1983; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - "Commissioning the Future", 1983; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Creating the Welfare State, 1982; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Creating the Welfare State, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Critical Crossings: American Studies International", 1991; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Current Developments in the Welfare State", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Death of Jane Addams, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - The Disability Businesss, 1992; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Disability Insurance and the Limits of American History", 1986; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "Disabled Policy: A Personal Postscript", 1992; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Disabled Policy, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Disabled Policy, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Disabled Policy, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - The Dread Disease: Cancer and Modern American Culture, 1987; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Dying for Work, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Family Policy and the Economy", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Feeble-Minded in our Midst, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - "Finding Work: Some Trends, Predictions and Laments for the 1980s", 1981; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - The First Social Security Crisis, 1983; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - From Company Doctors to Managed Care, 2000; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - George Bush and the Americans with Disabilities Act, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Historical Development of Social Insurance in the U.S.", 1994; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Historical Perspectives on Governmental Responses to Disability: An Overview Paper", 1976; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "Historical Preface to the ADA", 1994; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - "A Historical Preface to the ADA", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "History as an influence over American Disability Policy", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "History of Public Policy and Reality", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - "How to Think About the Welfare State", 1991; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "The Insecurity of Privatization", 1996; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Labor Force Participation Among Disabled Persons", 1990; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "Lessons from the VR/SSA Experience", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "Man of the People: A Life of Harry S Truman", 1996; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Mary E. Switzer: The Entrepreneur Within the Federal Bureaucracy", 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "A National Agenda for the Eighties", 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - New Deal Liberal, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "Overarching Issues in Disability Policy, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "The Passion and Politics of Phillip Burton", 1996; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Pittied, But Not Entitled", 1995; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - "Playing Politics with Disabled Persons: Public Policy Toward Rehabilitation of the Occupationally Disabled", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Politics and Professors, The Public Historian, 1979; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "Politics of Mental Retardation During the Kennedy Administration", 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Poverty of Welfare Reform, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The Presidency of Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1992; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Promoting the Welfare of Americans in the Eighties", 1981; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Professionals as Providers: Some Thoughts on Disability and Ideology:, 1984; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "Public Policy Toward Rehabilitation of the Occupationally Disabled", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Quiet Revolution, 1984; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Quiet Revolution, 1984; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Regulating Society, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Revealing America's Welfare STate, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "The Roosevelt New Deal", 1986; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - "Save the Babies", 1991; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - "The Shadow of the Mills", 1989; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - "A Social Agenda for the Eighties", 1981; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Social Influences on Rehabilitation Planning: Introductory Remarks", 1984; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Social Security and the Financing of the American State", 1994; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Social Security: The First Half-Century", 1998; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "The Social Welfare History State", 1990; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - The Social Welfare History State, 1990; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Some Thoughts on Disability as a Public Policy Problem", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - State and Party in America's New Deal, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Strachan and the Limits of the Federal Government", 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "The Struggle for Compromise: SSDI, 1935-1986", Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Testimony on Disability Policy and History Ways and Means: Social Security, 2000; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - The Transformation of Old Age Security, 1988; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - The Transformation of Social Security, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Unemployment Loopholes, 1981; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - The Unintended Consequences of Medicare, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Viewpoint, 1982; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Welfare Reform in the 1950s, 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Widening the Field, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Wilbur Cohen and American Social Reform, 1989; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "Wilbur Cohen and America's Welfare State", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "Wilbur Cohen and the Welfare State in Ike's America", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - "Wilbur J. Cohen and the Welfare State in Ike's Administration", Undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "1984 Humanities and Public Life Colloquium", Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Policy documents, 1965-1999; Series 7 Subseries 3; 1.5 Linear Feet
    Materials in this subseries relate to public policy material that Edward Berkowitz was involved with. This includes the materials from the MFUA. materials date from 1965-1999.
    Materials are arranged chronologically.
    - R-4 (POW), 1965-1978; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - R-19 (Twins), 1965-1991; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - R-4 (POW) followups, 1980-1999; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - R-4 (POW) follow ups, 1990-1999; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - CVs and Membership, 1980-1995; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - MFUA, 1965; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - MFUA, 1966; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - MFUA, 1967; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - MFUA, 1968; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - MFUA, 1969; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - MFUA, 1970; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - MFUA, 1971; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - MFUA, 1972; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - MFUA, 1973; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - MFUA, 1974; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - MFUA, 1975; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - MFUA, 1976; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - MFUA, 1977-1979; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - MFUA, 1981; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - MFUA, 1982; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - MFUA - Jablon Testimony regarding radiation, 1982-1992; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - MFUA, 1983; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - MFUA, 1984; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - MFUA, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - MFUA, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - MFUA, 1987; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - MFUA, 1988; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - MFUA, 1989; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - MFUA, 1990; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - MFUA, 1991; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - MFUA, 1992; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - MFUA, 1993; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - MFUA, 1994; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - MFUA, 1995; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - MFUA, 1996; Series 7 Subseries3 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Bibliography of the Medical Follow-Up, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Veterans, 1965-1988; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Class material, 1998-1999; RG0073 Series 8; Eleven spiral bound notebooks with syllabi for class notes from History department courses in fulfillment of PhD coursework.
  Class notes taken by Christopher Bright while attending history department classes.
  - HIST 220 Business history, Fall 1999 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 1)
  - HIST 101.11 History of nuclear arms race, Spring 1998 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Cold War, Fall 1998 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - HIST 177 Jackson era 19th century, Spring 1999 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - HIST 184 Civil War, Spring 2001 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - HIST 184 Civil War and reconstruction, Fall 1999 (Box Series 8 Box 1, Folder 10-11)